It's one of, this is one of the reasons I recovered from it.
And by the way, it's much better to not have TDS.
I'm happier, I'm healthier, more successful.
I even think I got a little more attractive
after I got rid of my Trump derangement syndrome, yes.
You know, I watched, I'm a reporter in Seattle,
and frankly, I could not care any less
what any of you have to say about this meeting.
Could not care any less.
We're not here for you.
I'm not here to convince any of you
that Antifa is a real thing,
because if you have not come to that conclusion by now,
you are never gonna come to that conclusion
because you don't wanna see it.
And you're gonna go and you're gonna say
it's a bunch of right-wing conservative influencers
who are here spinning a tale.
I was one of you.
I was a mainstream reporter in Seattle for 10 years.
I was a TV reporter on the streets doing my job,
and I was still assaulted by Antifa.
So it's not about being conservative.
It's about people who go there and show what they're doing.
And when I saw after all those years
that the media wouldn't be honest about what was happening,
that Democratic politicians wouldn't be honest
about what was happening, I thought, well, gosh,
if they're not being honest about that,
maybe they're not being honest about President Trump either.
And it opened my mind to just looking at things
for what they were.
And now I find you quite funny, actually.
Now I'm, it's like I said, I'm much happier about it.
But for me, again, I could not care any less
the stories that they go to print.
This is what I care about.
We have three and a half years.
Nothing is guaranteed,
although I think if Democrats keep it up,
we'll probably have Republican presidents
for the next three decades.
But nothing is guaranteed.
And so what I want to see over the next three and a half years
is a full court press to dismantle Antifa once and for all
in a meaningful way.
I know, Andy, we talked before this about some ideas.
That's really what we want to,
I don't care what the media says.
I don't care what Democrats say.
They will never wake up to this fact.
So we want the federal government
to take as many of these cases as possible.
Look at the interstate travel between Portland and Seattle
when it comes to these people
who are committing violent acts.
And hopefully in three and a half years,
they will be a shell of their former selves.
And it's Antifa and many others, unfortunately.
There are many others, bad ones.
Most have been named terrorist organizations.
There are a couple that we're going to,
but I think we've got it pretty well covered.
But there are many others,
but very specifically today's Antifa, and it's really bad.
And we're going to get it cleaned up.
Andy, did you have something?
Thank you very much.
I'm glad you no longer have TDS.
I feel very good about that.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. President and members of the cabinet.
I have a lot of gratitude
and a little bit about my background.
I'm born in Portland, Oregon from there.
And growing up, it's always been left-wing, very progressive
and I liked it.
It had cafes and artists
and those who lived a bohemian lifestyle.
And in 2016, I was a graduate student at Portland State
studying political science.
I was an editor at the student paper there,
a very progressive paper.
And I was assigned to cover
the election night demonstrations.
Well, the elections night protests turned to riots,
three days of violent rioting in Portland.
And it was the first time that I saw groups dressed in black
with their faces covered.
This was four years before COVID.
Some of them were waving the black flag of anarchism,
some the red flag of Marxism.
And within seconds, they would ravage one street
to another, to another, to another.
And the next day I would read the legacy media,
which I still read at that time and looked forward to,
and I looked up to those journalists.
And I was really shocked to see that the narrative
was that these, in my view,
anti-democratic political violence
was legitimate acts of protest because people were,
they were concerned about racism or all these other lies.
And so for the next four years,
I just continued going out with my video camera.
I thought, look, people can ignore what I write
because of spin, but videos can quite speak for themselves.
And in 2019, it led to me nearly losing my life.
I was covering another Antifa protest turn riot,
at that point had been routine in Portland.
And then I was ambushed in a mob beating
and I had never been in a fight.
I didn't even realize that I was being assaulted
until seconds in.
And the punches came from everywhere on my head and my face.
And I was bleeding out of my eyes and ears.
And then they threw all the drinks in my eyes
to humiliate me further and to laugh at me.
And I was rushed to the hospital in a ambulance and CT scan.
And I had subarachnoid hemorrhage,
which is bleeding in the brain and nearly died.
And after surviving that, the.